nvish.com 2009-04-13

# NVISH | IT Outsourcing Company and Software Development Solutions

## Our privacy policy is straightforward: 

NVISH is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. Our privacy policy is straightforward - We do not collect/store your personal information, when you visit our website(s), unless you volunteer to provide that information to us. .

The following provides an overview of how we protect your privacy during your visit, and handle the information we gather.

Information on our website(s) is gathered in two ways: (1) Information stored automatically (for example, through our site's technology); and (2) Information collected with consent (for example, when you voluntarily provide information).

## Information Collected and Stored Automatically

We collect information from you, when you visit our website(s), to browse, read, or download information. Even if you do not register for any of our services, we gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and/or to administer our Web site. This helps us identify the pages which our users are visiting. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information. This implies we track users’ sessions but not the users. The users remain anonymous.

The kind of information that we may gather automatically includes the type of browser you are using (e.g. Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of Operating System you are using (e.g. Windows '98 or Mac OS) or the domain name of your Internet Service Provider (e.g. AOL, Satyam Online, Comcast, VSNL, etc.), the date and time of your visit, and the pages you visit. We utilize this non-personally identifiable information to primarily improve our website(s) design, content, and browsing experience.

This site may contain links to other sites. NIVSH Group is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

## Personal Information Collected

We collect your personal information, only if you provide it voluntarily. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected include name, address, E-mail address, and information about your interests in using various services. For example, you might submit your name and e-mail address to subscribe to any of our services, or to ask for any quote, or to send us your feedback. The information you provide is not given or sold to any private organizations or private persons.

## Contacting us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, NVISH's information practices, or your dealings with NVISH, you can contact us using this form, or write to us at: this form, or write to us at:

**NVISH Solutions INC**  
DLF Info City  
First Floor, Tower E   
Chandigarh Technology Park   
Chandigarh 160101  
Email: [info@nvish.com](mailto:info@nvish.com)

With respect to our privacy practices as a financial institution and our compliance with this Privacy Policy, NVISH is regulated by the Panchkula Court.

##  Our Mission 

Create, innovate, and deploy business solutions that leverage the best in technology to increase the competitive advantage and business performance of our clients.

##   Team NVISH- An Asset

Our employees are our most valued assets. Without them we couldn’t have delivered value to our clients. Our employees continue to be the cornerstone of our success.

## NVISH offerings

NVISH defines, designs, and delivers technology-driven business solutions and services that help companies across the globe achieve better business performance.
